export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2017 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1612q.pdf",
        solution: "1701a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO Istanbul" },
            { name: "Ivane Gokadze", affiliation: "Georgia, L.T.D. School 1" },
            { name: "Gocha Gokadze", affiliation: "Georgia, L.T.D. School 1" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Vivek Mehra", affiliation: "Mumbai, India" },
            { name: "Nail Turhan", affiliation: "Yahyali Mustafa Koyuncu Fen Lisesi, Kayseri" },
            { name: "Eyyüp Bahtiyar Çekmelelioğlu", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Fakih Karademir", affiliation: "Utrecht, The Netherlands" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "İbrahim Suat Evren", affiliation: "Denizli" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Benjamin Edun", affiliation: "METU, Ankara" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1701q.pdf",
        solution: "1702a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Vivek Mehra", affiliation: "Mumbai, India" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Vanio Beccaccioli", affiliation: "Terni, Italy" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Ivane Gokadze", affiliation: "Tsereteli State University, Georgia" },
            { name: "Gocha Gokadze", affiliation: "L.T.D. School 1, Georgia" },
            { name: "Adem Limani", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Paolo Perfetti", affiliation: "University of Rome Tor Vergata, Italy" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1702q.pdf",
        solution: "1703a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Batuhan Bayır", affiliation: "İzmir Betontaş Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Muhammetnur Bagbekov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1703q.pdf",
        solution: "1704a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Vivek Mehra", affiliation: "Mumbai, India" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "İlker Can Çicek", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Kayra Uygun", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Onur Korkmaz", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Ahmet Alper Özüdoğru", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Batuhan Bayır", affiliation: "İzmir Betontaş Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1704q.pdf",
        solution: "1705a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "İlker Can Çicek", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Kayra Uygun", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Nurullah Giray Kuru", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Onur Korkmaz", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Ahmet Alper Özüdoğru", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mehmet Selahaddin Şentop", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mehmet Can Özdemir", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Emirhan İlhan", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Kerem Recep Gür", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Tilekbek Zhoroev", affiliation: "Erciyes University, Kayseri" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Osman Asil", affiliation: "Celal Bayar University" },
            { name: "Dovran Nurgeldiyev", affiliation: "Magtymguly Turkmen State University, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Adem Limani", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Batuhan Bayır", affiliation: "İzmir Betontaş Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Emine Yeşil Şahinkaya", affiliation: "Bursa" },
            { name: "Evan Luff", affiliation: "USA" },
            { name: "Eren Can Kızıldağ", affiliation: "Massachusetts Institute of Technology, USA" },
            { name: "Sümeyye Seren", affiliation: "Yıldız Technical University" },
            { name: "Allen Kruze", affiliation: "Florida, USA" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1705q.pdf",
        solution: "1706a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "İlker Can Çicek", affiliation: "İstanbul Lisesi" },
            { name: "Kayra Uygun", affiliation: "Ankara Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Onur Korkmaz", affiliation: "İzmir Fen Lisesi" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1706q.pdf",
        solution: "1707a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Leo Chin Ho", affiliation: "National University of Singapore, Singapore" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yildirim", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1707q.pdf",
        solution: "1709a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Mehmet Ali Yıldırım", affiliation: "Florya Final Anadolu Lisesi, Istanbul" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Vivek Mehra", affiliation: "Mumbai, India" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Xagani Gasımov", affiliation: "Baku, Azerbaijan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Bogaziçi University" },
            { name: "Dovran Nurgeldiyev", affiliation: "Lebap, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "F. Wallner", affiliation: "Germany" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Eren Can Kızıldağ", affiliation: "Massachusetts Institute of Technology, USA" },
            { name: "Semih Zaman", affiliation: "Özel Enka Fen ve Teknoloji Lisesi, Kocaeli" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1709q.pdf",
        solution: "1710a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Batuhan Bayır", affiliation: "Ankara University" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Bogaziçi University" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Xagani Gasımov", affiliation: "Baku, Azerbaijan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1710q.pdf",
        solution: "1711a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Bogaziçi University" },
            { name: "Batuhan Bayır", affiliation: "Ankara University" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2017,
        question: "1711q.pdf",
        solution: "1712a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
            { name: "Vivek Mehra", affiliation: "Mumbai, India" },
            { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Ömer Avcı", affiliation: "Boğaziçi University, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Paolo Perfetti", affiliation: "University of Rome Tor Vergata, Italy" },
            { name: "Baygeldi Cholukov", affiliation: "S. Turkmenbashy State School, Ashgabat, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Muhammetnur Bagbekov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Serdar Hojayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Batuhan Bayır", affiliation: "Ankara University" },
            { name: "İbrahim Fırat Yoğurtçu", affiliation: "Çağaloğlu Anadolu Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Berkay Ünlü", affiliation: "Dokuz Eylül University, İzmir" }
        ]
    }
];
